mirror8.net 2014-11-21

# Download uPlayer Free

## Overview of Our Privacy Policy

We supply free entertainment and utility software. Our Products may include Toolbars, which add search functionality to your browser. They also allow one click access to news and our offers. We refer to our software and Products throughout this agreement as our “Services”.

We offer our Services to you in exchange for your agreement to view promotions, advertisements, or participate in other offers. We also offer you the opportunity to download third-party software.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our online privacy practices regarding:

  * Information we collect
  * How we use the information
  * How we share your information, if at all
  * Your choices

We may make available shorter versions of this Privacy Policy. We also may supplement this policy for specific Services. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our summary this policy will govern. Where there is a conflict between this policy and our supplement, the supplement will govern.

We may change this privacy policy. If we change this policy we will post the changes to this privacy statement, our websites’ homepages, and other places we deem appropriate. We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

## Some Terms We Use in This Policy

Offers include e-mail, promotions, advertisements contests and third-party software presented by our Partners and us.

Personally Identifiable Information (PII) is any information that identifies or could be used to identify, contact or locate you. It also includes your credit card number.

Partner is an advertiser, or other entity with whom we have a business relationship to provide Offers.

Service includes, but is not limited to, our screensaver, wallpaper, game, animated gif, clip art, buddy icon, greeting card, browser skin, font, desktop theme, html editor, sound effect, social networking, storage, and calendar software, as well as our Toolbars.

Subsidiary is an entity wholly owned or related to uPlayer.us.com.

User means an individual that has accessed the Sites on which we host our Products or Services.

We and Our refer to uPlayer.us.com and its subsidiaries.

You and Your refer to each user and his or her agents.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee it’s absolutely security.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience—Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve our website—We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

**E-mail Offers**

By providing your e-mail address, and choosing to receive our Offers, you agree to receive e-mails from us. Should you have any questions or concerns, or if you would like to discontinue receiving Offers, simply email us at contactus@uPlayer.us.com and ask us to remove you from our lists. You will only receive Offers via e-mail from us and our Partners if you have indicated that you would like to receive them.

**Testimonials**

We post testimonials on our Sites. Testimonials may contain Personally Identifiable Information. We will obtain your consent via email prior to posting the testimonial or comment.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that sites and service providers may transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser. They enable the site and service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. You can turn off cookies in your settings at any time.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we use Web beacons or Pixels?

Yes. We and our Partners employ a software technology that helps us better manage content on our site. Web beacons or Pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They track your online Web movement. We embed Pixels invisibly on Web pages. They are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixels to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

Some of the Partner Offers may also use Pixels. We have no control over our partners’ Pixels. We also have no control over how they use information collected.

## Do we collect software information?

Yes. We employ a technology that allows us to determine the operating systems you are using and to view your computer’s registry. Software installed on your computer has unique registry keys. By viewing your registry, we are able to detect whether you have a compatible operating system, compatible versions of DirectX, and Flash Player installed. We use your registry information to determine whether our software offers are compatible with software already present on your PC. We do not tie registry information gathered to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

## Do we collect hardware information?

Yes. Your computer’s operating system also stores hardware information that we examine to determine your computer’s hardware configuration including the amount of memory and the type of video card your computer has, as well as the speed of your processor. We use the information to determine whether our software offers are compatible with your computer hardware. We do not tie hardware information to our customers’ Personally Identifiable Information.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personally identifiable information to outside parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or other’s rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## How Do Toolbars Affect Your Browser And Operating System?

Toolbars install into your Internet browser and allow you to search the Internet. If you consent to make a toolbar your default search, your Internet browser default search feature will be set and you will access search services (i) by entering queries in your browser search box; (ii) by entering queries in your browser address bar, and/or (iii) in response to misspelled, incorrectly formatted or unresolved DNS submissions in your browser address bar.

Toolbars do not affect your operating system. Toolbars can be removed at any time. For more information regarding toolbars, please view our Terms of Service.

If you would like to reset your browser, follow the General Toolbar Uninstall Instructions below.

## General Uninstall Instructions

If, for any reason at all, you decide you no longer want the downloaded software or offers on your computer, you can easily uninstall them at any time. We’re sorry to see you go!

The following are general instructions regarding the software uninstallation process:

**For Firefox Users**

  * Go to the orange “Firefox” menu located at the top left of your Firefox browser window
  * Select “Add-ons” to open the Add-ons Manager
  * Under “Extensions” click the name of the add-on that you would like to disable or remove
  * Select “Disable” or “Remove”
  * Select the “Restart Now” link to restart Firefox
  * That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

**For Windows 7 & Vista Users**

  * Go to the ”Start Menu” located at the bottom right of your screen
  * Select ”Control Panel”
  * Under ”Programs” click “Uninstall a Program”
  * Right click on the program you wish to remove, then click ”Uninstall/Change“
  * Follow the uninstallation steps
  * That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

**For Windows XP Users**

  * Go to the ”Start Menu” located at the bottom right of your screen
  * Select ”Control Panel”
  * Click “Add or Remove Programs“
  * Click the program you wish to remove, then click “Remove” or “Change/Remove“
  * Follow the uninstallation steps
  * That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

**For Windows 95, 98, Me, NT, 2000, and XP Users In Classic View**

  * From the “Start Menu,” select “Settings,” and then “Control Panel”
  * Double-click the “Add/Remove Programs” icon
  * Select the program you wish to remove and click on the “Remove” or “Change/Remove” button
  * Follow the prompts to finish the uninstallation of the software
  * That’s it! You will now have successfully uninstalled the software.

*Note: After you have uninstalled the software, certain data such as folders, files, registry keys, and cookies, may remain on your computer. We recommend that you clear your cookies after uninstalling.>

If for any reason you are having difficulties uninstalling your software, please reach us via email at [contactus@uPlayer.us.com](mailto:contactus@uPlayer.us.com).

## How do I opt out? 

We currently do not send messages to or collect data from users. If at any time we do contact you, it would only be for support reasons. If in that regard, you would like stop receiving messages or notifications, you can click on an unsubscribe link from any message we provide to no longer receive our messages.

If you would like to be removed from our system, you can reach us via email at [contactus@uPlayer.us.com](mailto:contactus@uPlayer.us.com).

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy, we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account via the “Sign In” link on the top right of the home page. Then click on ‘Page Settings’ and then go to the ‘Account’ section.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

## Terms & Conditions

Please also visit our “Terms of Service” section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Terms Of Service.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

## Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may Contact Us at:

uPlayer.us.com  
Tightrope Interactive  
268 Bush St. #3040  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
415-787-4144  

**Last Updated: October 8, 2012**
